<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API Reference on</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/</link><description>Recent content in API Reference on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AccessEntry</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/eks/v1alpha1/accessentry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/eks/v1alpha1/accessentry/</guid><description>eks.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc eks-controller/apis/v1alpha1#AccessEntry Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind AccessEntry ListKind AccessEntryList Plural accessentries Singular accessentry An access entry allows an IAM principal (user or role) to access your cluster. Access entries can replace the need to maintain the aws-auth ConfigMap for authentication.</description></item><item><title>AccessPoint</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/efs/v1alpha1/accesspoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/efs/v1alpha1/accesspoint/</guid><description>efs.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc efs-controller/apis/v1alpha1#AccessPoint Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind AccessPoint ListKind AccessPointList Plural accesspoints Singular accesspoint Spec fileSystemID: string fileSystemRef: from: name: string namespace: string posixUser: gid: integer secondaryGIDs: - integer uid: integer rootDirectory: creationInfo: ownerGID: integer ownerUID: integer permissions: string path: string tags: - key: string value: string Field Description fileSystemIDOptional stringThe ID of the EFS file system that the access point provides access to.</description></item><item><title>AccessPoint</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/s3control/v1alpha1/accesspoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/s3control/v1alpha1/accesspoint/</guid><description>s3control.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc s3control-controller/apis/v1alpha1#AccessPoint Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind AccessPoint ListKind AccessPointList Plural accesspoints Singular accesspoint An access point used to access a bucket.
Spec accountID: string bucket: string bucketAccountID: string name: string publicAccessBlockConfiguration: blockPublicACLs: boolean blockPublicPolicy: boolean ignorePublicACLs: boolean restrictPublicBuckets: boolean vpcConfiguration: vpcID: string Field Description accountIDRequired stringThe Amazon Web Services account ID for the account that owns the specifiedaccess point.</description></item><item><title>Account</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/organizations/v1alpha1/account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/organizations/v1alpha1/account/</guid><description>organizations.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc organizations-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Account Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Account ListKind AccountList Plural accounts Singular account Contains information about an Amazon Web Services account that is a member of an organization.
Spec email: string iamUserAccessToBilling: string name: string roleName: string tags: - key: string value: string Field Description emailRequired stringThe email address of the owner to assign to the new member account.</description></item><item><title>ACL</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/memorydb/v1alpha1/acl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/memorydb/v1alpha1/acl/</guid><description>memorydb.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc memorydb-controller/apis/v1alpha1#ACL Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind ACL ListKind ACLList Plural acls Singular acl An Access Control List. You can authenticate users with Access Contol Lists. ACLs enable you to control cluster access by grouping users. These Access control lists are designed as a way to organize access to clusters.</description></item><item><title>Activity</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/sfn/v1alpha1/activity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/sfn/v1alpha1/activity/</guid><description>sfn.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc sfn-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Activity Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Activity ListKind ActivityList Plural activities Singular activity Spec name: string tags: - key: string value: string Field Description nameRequired stringThe name of the activity to create.</description></item><item><title>Addon</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/eks/v1alpha1/addon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/eks/v1alpha1/addon/</guid><description>eks.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc eks-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Addon Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Addon ListKind AddonList Plural addons Singular addon An Amazon EKS add-on. For more information, see Amazon EKS add-ons (https://docs.aws.amazon.com/eks/latest/userguide/eks-add-ons.html) in the Amazon EKS User Guide.
Spec addonVersion: string clientRequestToken: string clusterName: string clusterRef: from: name: string namespace: string configurationValues: string name: string podIdentityAssociations: - roleARN: string serviceAccount: string resolveConflicts: string serviceAccountRoleARN: string serviceAccountRoleRef: from: name: string namespace: string tags: {} Field Description addonVersionOptional stringThe version of the add-on.</description></item><item><title>AdoptedResource</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/common/v1alpha1/adoptedresource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/common/v1alpha1/adoptedresource/</guid><description>services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc runtime/apis/core/v1alpha1#AdoptedResource Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind AdoptedResource ListKind AdoptedResourceList Plural adoptedresources Singular adoptedresource Spec aws: additionalKeys: {} arn: string nameOrID: string kubernetes: group: string kind: string metadata: annotations: {} generateName: string labels: {} name: string namespace: string ownerReferences: - apiVersion: string blockOwnerDeletion: boolean controller: boolean kind: string name: string uid: string Field Description awsRequired objectAWSIdentifiers provide all unique ways to reference an AWS resource.</description></item><item><title>AlertManagerDefinition</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/prometheusservice/v1alpha1/alertmanagerdefinition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/prometheusservice/v1alpha1/alertmanagerdefinition/</guid><description>prometheusservice.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc prometheusservice-controller/apis/v1alpha1#AlertManagerDefinition Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind AlertManagerDefinition ListKind AlertManagerDefinitionList Plural alertmanagerdefinitions Singular alertmanagerdefinition Spec configuration: string workspaceID: string workspaceRef: from: name: string namespace: string Field Description configurationRequired string workspaceIDOptional stringThe ID of the workspace to add the alert manager definition to.</description></item><item><title>Alias</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/kms/v1alpha1/alias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/kms/v1alpha1/alias/</guid><description>kms.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc kms-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Alias Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Alias ListKind AliasList Plural aliases Singular alias Spec name: string targetKeyID: string targetKeyRef: from: name: string namespace: string Field Description nameRequired stringSpecifies the alias name.</description></item></channel></rss>