<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>API Reference on</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/</link><description>Recent content in API Reference on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ACL</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/memorydb/v1alpha1/acl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/memorydb/v1alpha1/acl/</guid><description>memorydb.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc memorydb-controller/apis/v1alpha1#ACL Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind ACL ListKind ACLList Plural acls Singular acl An Access Control List. You can authenticate users with Access Contol Lists. ACLs enable you to control cluster access by grouping users. These Access control lists are designed as a way to organize access to clusters.</description></item><item><title>Activity</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/sfn/v1alpha1/activity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/sfn/v1alpha1/activity/</guid><description>sfn.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc sfn-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Activity Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Activity ListKind ActivityList Plural activities Singular activity Spec name: string tags: - key: string value: string Field Description nameRequired stringThe name of the activity to create.</description></item><item><title>Addon</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/eks/v1alpha1/addon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/eks/v1alpha1/addon/</guid><description>eks.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc eks-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Addon Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Addon ListKind AddonList Plural addons Singular addon An Amazon EKS add-on.
Spec addonVersion: string clientRequestToken: string clusterName: string clusterRef: from: name: string name: string resolveConflicts: string serviceAccountRoleARN: string tags: {} Field Description addonVersionOptional stringThe version of the add-on.</description></item><item><title>AdoptedResource</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/common/v1alpha1/adoptedresource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/common/v1alpha1/adoptedresource/</guid><description>services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc runtime/apis/core/v1alpha1#AdoptedResource Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind AdoptedResource ListKind AdoptedResourceList Plural adoptedresources Singular adoptedresource Spec aws: additionalKeys: {} arn: string nameOrID: string kubernetes: group: string kind: string metadata: annotations: {} generateName: string labels: {} name: string namespace: string ownerReferences: - apiVersion: string blockOwnerDeletion: boolean controller: boolean kind: string name: string uid: string Field Description awsRequired objectAWSIdentifiers provide all unique ways to reference an AWS resource.</description></item><item><title>Alias</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/kms/v1alpha1/alias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/kms/v1alpha1/alias/</guid><description>kms.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc kms-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Alias Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Alias ListKind AliasList Plural aliases Singular alias Spec name: string targetKeyID: string Field Description nameRequired stringSpecifies the alias name. This value must begin with alias/ followed by a name, such as alias/ExampleAlias.</description></item><item><title>Alias</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/lambda/v1alpha1/alias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/lambda/v1alpha1/alias/</guid><description>lambda.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc lambda-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Alias Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Alias ListKind AliasList Plural aliases Singular alias Spec description: string functionName: string functionVersion: string name: string routingConfig: additionalVersionWeights: {} Field Description descriptionOptional stringA description of the alias.</description></item><item><title>API</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/apigatewayv2/v1alpha1/api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/apigatewayv2/v1alpha1/api/</guid><description>apigatewayv2.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc apigatewayv2-controller/apis/v1alpha1#API Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind API ListKind APIList Plural apis Singular api Represents an API.
Spec apiKeySelectionExpression: string basepath: string body: string corsConfiguration: allowCredentials: boolean allowHeaders: - string allowMethods: - string allowOrigins: - string exposeHeaders: - string maxAge: integer credentialsARN: string description: string disableExecuteAPIEndpoint: boolean disableSchemaValidation: boolean failOnWarnings: boolean name: string protocolType: string routeKey: string routeSelectionExpression: string tags: {} target: string version: string Field Description apiKeySelectionExpressionOptional string basepathOptional string bodyOptional string corsConfigurationOptional objectRepresents a CORS configuration.</description></item><item><title>App</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/sagemaker/v1alpha1/app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/sagemaker/v1alpha1/app/</guid><description>sagemaker.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc sagemaker-controller/apis/v1alpha1#App Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind App ListKind AppList Plural apps Singular app Spec appName: string appType: string domainID: string resourceSpec: instanceType: string sageMakerImageARN: string sageMakerImageVersionARN: string tags: - key: string value: string userProfileName: string Field Description appNameRequired stringThe name of the app.</description></item><item><title>Authorizer</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/apigatewayv2/v1alpha1/authorizer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/apigatewayv2/v1alpha1/authorizer/</guid><description>apigatewayv2.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc apigatewayv2-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Authorizer Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Authorizer ListKind AuthorizerList Plural authorizers Singular authorizer Represents an authorizer.
Spec apiID: string apiRef: from: name: string authorizerCredentialsARN: string authorizerPayloadFormatVersion: string authorizerResultTtlInSeconds: integer authorizerType: string authorizerURI: string enableSimpleResponses: boolean identitySource: - string identityValidationExpression: string jwtConfiguration: audience: - string issuer: string name: string Field Description apiIDOptional string apiRefOptional objectAWSResourceReferenceWrapper provides a wrapper around *AWSResourceReference type to provide more user friendly syntax for references using &amp;lsquo;from&amp;rsquo; field Ex: APIIDRef: from: name: my-api apiRef.</description></item><item><title>Backup</title><link>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/dynamodb/v1alpha1/backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://aws-controllers-k8s.github.io/community/reference/dynamodb/v1alpha1/backup/</guid><description>dynamodb.services.k8s.aws/v1alpha1
Type Link GoDoc dynamodb-controller/apis/v1alpha1#Backup Metadata Property Value Scope Namespaced Kind Backup ListKind BackupList Plural backups Singular backup Spec backupName: string tableName: string Field Description backupNameRequired stringSpecified name for the backup. tableNameRequired stringThe name of the table.</description></item></channel></rss>